Look at
Triple kill dyer's middle tower is not what it used to be
That is
The middle tower has fallen
Radiant top tower is under attack
Shadows take us
Shut down
You got hands on experience
What have you
Tier's middle tower is under attack
The axe is out
Top tower is under attack
So far
Dyer's middle tower is under attack
The ingredient's top tower is under attack
Radiance top tower has fallen to the
I said
You get nothing for day
Sir
Dyer's bottom tower is taking many wounds
Dyer's bottom tower has fallen
Shall carry no more
Dyer's middle tower is not what it used to be
That is for certain
The red mist spreads at radiance middle tower
Radiance little tower is under attack
Broken
Tire structures are fortified
And found the weakness in dyer's bottom tower
It turns out if you hit it enough
It will fall
Has slain
Dyer's middle tower is not what it used to be
The diers were fortified
Super super fortified like you can tower is under attack
Tires middle tower is under attack
Tires little tower
The top tower is under attack
Dyer's agent is under attack